



SUMMARY

Software Engineer with +2 years of experience in a corporate environment. Outgoing and innovative, I am extremely proficient at coming up with creative solutions. Have a Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science from one of the best universities.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 — 2018 Application Developer

Enterprise Architecture
Canadian Imperial Bank of Commerce

Assist architects with POC project. Help governance team design new process. Create efficient communication process within organization.

2015 — **2015 Web Developer**

Qingdao Micro Wisdom Info Tech Co. Ltd

Researched a practicable and low-cost algorithm by using open source JavaScript Libraries and cheap map data.

2016 - 2016 Calculus Tutor

Help tutee with weekly assignments by doing sample questions and explain the concept behind each step

2003 – 2005 **Volunteer Chess Instructor**

Chess in the library program

Help local children improve their chess skill. Organize tournament within the group.

EDUCATION

2015 — 2019 Bachelor of Science In Software Engineering (Co-op)

University of Toronto

SKILLS

Technical

Java/Python

C/C++

Haskell

HTML/CSS

SQL

Hadoop

GIT/SVN

Interpersonal

Innovative
Creativity
Communication
Team Works
Leadership
Adaptability

Languages

English

Mandarin Chinese

PROJECTS

Web-based offline map Personal Page Online Trip Organization App

INTERESTS

Rubik's cube History Swimming Video Games